JASON WOSAK

267.456.3528 jason.wosak@rcn.com

OVERVIEW

I am a multi-disciplined Graphic Designer with 14 years experience in Multimedia, Print, and Apparel design. Although initially graphically focused, I have been inspired and energized by programming multimedia using Flash for 8 years, with a thorough backround in Actionscript 2.0, utilizing XML, Video, and Object Oriented Programming structure. I am also proficient in ASP.Net, ASP, SQL, ColdFusion and javascript.

My best assets include my intense creative energy, well-rounded real world experience, pride and enthusiasm for my profession and dedication to craft. The ability to quickly understand and embrace emerging technologies has always been a strong point. I have extensive experience in supervisory positions. I am a self starter who is accustomed to meeting deadlines, solving problems and hard work.

HISTORY

FMP MEDIA

Graphic Designer, Multimedia Programmer

SOLUTIONS

(2000-PRESENT)

I visually design and program multimedia applications, database integrated web applications, streaming media scripting, presentations and kiosks. We are a world-class facilitator of business communications for Fortune 500 companies, producing video, meetings & events, web applications, multimedia and webcasting. I have experience in live-show production as a presentation technician, doing international meetings, and maintaining content for the show, and organizing for redistribution through CD or online.

ZAGS ADVANCED

GRAPHIC DESIGNER, PRODUCTION MANAGER

GRAPHICS

Designing artwork for screenprinted t-shirts, signs and custom cut vinyl, as well as and website layout

1998-2000

incorporating flash animations. I managed the production crew for in-house t-shirt printing.

SIR SPEEDY PRINTING

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

1997-1998

I was responsible for in-house graphic design, color proofing, color separation, imposition, trapping, and typesetting for offset printing and digital output. This was the 6th busiest Sir Speedy in the country.

FLAT ON YOUR BACK

Graphic Designer, Production Manager

1995-1997

I was responsible for the design, layout, color-separations for screenprinting. I managed the screenprinting workflow, and personnel as well, due to my knowledge of all aspects of the screenprinting process.

T-Bones Records

ART DIRECTOR, GRAPHIC DESIGNER, SCREENPRINTING

1992-1995

(1995-NOW FREELANCE)

My best friend and I left college to start this independent record label, I was the visual creative side of the business. I was in charge of artistic direction, and execution of every CD layout and design, maintaining and designing the website (www.tbonesrecords.com), promotions, t-shirts, flyers, stickers.

I was instrumental in implementing the merchandising as a reliable revenue stream. I created an in-house screenprinting studio, for apparel and stickers, and used local contacts to generate business.

I have designed and layed out over 28 CD's packaging with ad support. Including a Grammy nominated release for "Afroman". I still maintain the website informally, and we release about an album a year.

U.S. NAVY

OPERATIONS SPECIALIST, CIC WATCH SUPERVISOR.

1986-1990

This position that was responsible for radar, navigation, and communication between ships and within the ship. This is a job that demanded precise communication, and attention to detail. I was placed in a supervisory position normally reserved for more senior personnel after 2 years.

JASON WOSAK

267.456.3528 jason.wosak@rcn.com

SKILLSETS

GRAPHIC DESIGN

- Photoshop (Imageready), Illustrator: 13 years, master level knowledge.
- Quark xPress, InDesign (Pagemaker): 10 years, master level knowledge.
- Powerpoint, Acrobat: 7 years, advanced knowledge.
- 3d Max, AfterEffects, Painter: creative working knowledge.

Multimedia / Web Programming LANGUAGES

- Actionscript (2.0): 7 years, master knowledge.
- ASP.Net, ASP, ColdFusion, HTML: 5 years, advanced knowledge.
- XML, CSS, SQL, Javascript: 5 years, good working knowledge.

Tools

- Macromedia Flash (8): 8 years, master knowledge.
- MS Visual Studio 2005, Dreamweaver: advanced knowledge.
- Flash Jugglor, Swishmax, AutoPlay Media Studio: good working knowledge.
- TopStyle, XML Spy
- SQL Server, IIS, Access, MySQL

VIDEO / STREAMING

MEDIA

- Vegas, SoundForge, Premiere, AfterEffects: 4 years, working knowledge.
- MediaCleaner, Sorenson Video Encoder, Flash Video Encoder
- Windows Media: encoding, streaming, indexing, scripting the Media control for interactivity within a web application.

EDUCATION

University of South Alabama

1990-1992

Concentration in graphic and fine arts.

Withdrew after second year to start business (T-Bones Records, above) with my best friend.

REFERENCES

Витсн Ѕмітн 1-302-420-8718

Director of Multimedia & Meetings

FMP Media Solutions

TIM RAMENOFSKY 1-818-200-3221

President, Music Producer

T-Bones Records

GRETCHEN RACHKO 1-484-252-1260

Multimedia & Video Producer

Independent (Formerly with DuPont)